Hi Victoria!
I wanted to give you a rundown of your project
for the next couple of weeks before our team meeting.
We're releasing the new app in four weeks and
need to make sure everyone is on the same page.
Do you mind drafting up a work plan for the next
month and getting feedback from the rest of the team?
Ah, sure.
I have no idea how to get started on this work.
I'm used to planning and execution, not brainstorming
different solutions and getting input from different individuals.
This problem has so many moving pieces.
I should ask my manager for help.
Everything okay?
I was just wondering if you could
help me get started on this work.
I'm having trouble breaking down all
the pieces of work that need to get done.
No worries at all.
There are a few different things we want to
evaluate when we're trying to solve a problem.
What are we trying to solve exactly?
What does the end goal look like,
and how do we get there?